bcu.org 2010-11-22

# BCU - Privacy Policy

**Notice of privacy practices for members  
** Important information about the personal data your credit union collects and how it is used. To assure the continued privacy and confidentiality of your personal financial information, your credit union observes the following practices and procedures:

**Text Banking / Account Alerts**  
Text Banking and Account Alerts top priority is the privacy of our users. The following is provided to address any concerns you may have. 

  * Text Banking and Account Alerts will never, under any circumstances, sell or distribute your cell phone number to third parties or Text Banking and Account Alerts clients for whom you have not approved.
  * Text Banking and Account Alerts will never directly market to you any services for which you have not opted in, either by cell phone, text message or email.
  * Text Banking and Account Alerts will never distribute any personal information about you, including your phone number, name, billing information or any other piece of identifying information.

If you have any questions, please call 1-800-388-7000 or send an email to [askBCU@BCU.org](mailto:askbcu@bcu.org)

**Information We Collect**  
In an effort to provide superior service to each Member in an accurate and timely fashion, BCU collects and maintains information about our Members. We understand that the nature of the information provided to us is highly personal and we respect our members' desire to maintain the privacy of such information. Therefore, we do not sell our member lists or member information to third parties, whether affiliated or not.

We collect non-public personal information about you from some or all of the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications, the Web site or other forms, such as your name, address, social security number, assets, income, telephone number and email address.
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage.
  * Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history. 

**Information We Disclose**  
We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial service companies with which we have joint marketing agreements. Sharing information with these affiliated companies enables us to inform you of products and services that could be of value to you. We may also disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted by law.

BCU will never, under any circumstances, sell or distribute your cell phone number to third parties or clients for whom you have not approved. BCU will never directly market to you any services for which you have not opted in, either by cell phone, text message or email to your cell phone. BCU will never distribute your cell phone number to any third party company. 

**Our Security Measures  
** We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees and officials who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your non-public personal information.

We appreciate the level of trust you place in us when you provide your personal and financial data. To continue earning that trust, BCU 's main priority is to maintain your right to privacy and respect the interests of our Members.

Should you decide to terminate your membership or become an inactive member, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice.

**Using our Secure Site**  
Data on the BCU Web servers is secure and protected. Our staff is trained to treat member information with the utmost confidentiality. BCU keeps the user information secure via Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and other types of encryption. This protection extends to feedback forms, product order forms and other online forms asking for personal information. Microsoft and Netscape browsers, version 4.0 and above, support such security protocols. 

**3rd Party Web Site Links**  
BCU websites may contain hyperlinks to other sites created and maintained by other organizations. When you click those links, you will be leaving the BCU Web site and viewing alternate Web sites not operated by the credit union. BCU does not regularly review materials posted on these linked sites and is not responsible for the content on them. BCU does not represent either the third party or the member if the two enter into a transaction. Privacy and security policies may differ from those practiced by BCU. Any decision of Web site visitors to view any of the linked Web sites is at their own risk.

**Privacy Policy Statement  
** The privacy policy is effective as of 6/1/2005. Changes to the privacy policy are updated on the web site and notated with an asterisk and revision date. Member Information can be updated by accessing online banking, selecting the update member profile link, and completing the required fields. If you have any questions about our organization, our privacy policy statement, or our practices on this site, please contact BCU via mail or telephone.

BCU  
P.O. Box 8133  
Vernon Hills, IL 60061  
800-388-7000
